Nice! That looks great on you!
I'm sure everyone will be
shocked when they see
just how fashionable
you are, Kageyama-kun!
Nii-san... Are you gonna
go out wearing that?
You'll let me borrow it sometime?
Er, I'm fine, thanks...
Huh? What the hell is that shirt?
Why did you take off your jacket?
Keep it on. Your school jacket
has higher defense points.
I think I might finally be popular.
Your time's finally arrived...
That's not a misunderstanding.
You've got the wrong idea.
You better realize that
before you get hurt.
What the...? No, really. What the eff?
What the hell is that design?!
Why were you wearing that
under your uniform?
It's so lame that I'm starting
to worry about you.
Just looking at it makes me uneasy.
Hey, is something really bothering you?
Are you just not thinking?
Did you happen to get that
on sale for dirt cheap?
Or are you wearing it because
you actually thought it was cool?
Are you okay?
You have such shit tast--
His energy is growing...
Is he gonna attack me?!
MOB MOB WOW! MOB MOB WOW!
I realized that my youth was grey
The root of this irritation is unknown
My brain runs parallel with this emotional train
Struggling adolescence
Don't disturb the subconscious mind
Who's that behind me?
Opposing ideas, distortion
Purge the sorrow
So, do what you can now.
My life
Finally
Break it down!!
(WANT) desire (YOUNG) and sincerity
(BURN) they begin to sprout (1) within my chest
(TRANCE) I won't awaken (CHANCE) but I want to
(STANCE) both sides of the coin
(1) are back-to-back
Accept me as I am
Conflicting freedom and relations
If they can become one
That smile will be
One and only "1"
MOB MOB WOW! MOB MOB WOW!
"Mob Psycho 100 III"
MOB MOB WOW!
One and only "1"
"Mob Psycho 100 III"
"Mob Psycho 100 "
MOB MOB WOW! MOB MOB WOW!
One and only "1"
"Divine Tree 3
- Dimple Is~"
This light...
Is it the power of Psycho Helmet-sama?
What's happening inside the Divine Tree?
It's so pretty...
Whew, I panicked for a sec.
I thought he was finally gonna blow.
What's wrong all of a sudden?
Are you that shocked?
Did you actually like that lame shirt?
Oh, now he's attacking.
Godly Barrier!
What the--?
He got blown away easier
than I thought he would.
No, really. What's wrong?
I don't feel any power from Shigeo.
He's totally empty and defenseless.
Did the Divine Tree suck his energy dry?
No. A moment ago, Shigeo was
releasing energy like a popped balloon.
Hey. Did you use up the rest of your energy?
On purpose? But why?
Did you lose all hope in me?
You don't feel like getting
through to me anymore?
You're going to let this end half-assed?
I even went through the trouble
of transforming into God Dimple.
Hey! Hello?
You sleeping, Shigeo?
What are you trying to do?
I thought you didn't want
to accept what I'm doing!
Now that I have godly powers,
how the hell are you gonna fight me
without your psychic powers?
Standing before you is a powerful enemy
unlike any you've faced before.
At this rate, it's all going to be over
with a little prick from my finger!
Hello?!
You're right. But you
won't actually do that.
I understand now.
When I talk to you, having powers
is just going to get in the way.
Now, we can finally talk.
See?
I knew I could trust you, Dimple.
Huh?
"Trust"
Trust?
Trust...?
Why?
Because you gave me your honest
opinion about this shirt.
Dimple, you're just Dimple.
Wait, wait, wait.
None of this makes sense.
You don't like how I'm doing things, right?
You okay with leaving me like this?
I'm... a dangerous evil spirit!
You're not dangerous, Dimple.
I figured it out.
Huh?
You just got carried away.
I think everyone goes through
something like that.
Master Reigen mentioned that, too.
That's not true.
This confidence that I have is backed up
with a bunch of hard work.
Don't compare me with some randos
that just get carried away.
I got carried away, too.
So... I get it.
Huh? Er, no, you're actually
way too modest, usually...
No.
I really did get carried away.
I'm sorry.
What do you mean, "sorry"?
You're not trying to win me over now
with this half-assed attempt, are you?
Back then, I'd gotten carried away
and didn't listen to what you had to say.
Why don't you give
your schemes a rest already?
We should've talked
everything out back then.
But I was so worried about
if I was popular or not
that I lost sight of what was
way more important.
I'm sorry, Dimple.
When it felt like you could finally do
what you always wanted to do,
finally get what you always longed for...
...you invited me.
You clearly could've
pulled this off on your own,
but you still invited me to join you.
And that... was the most important part.
This wasn't some scheme.
You just wanted to do what
you've always wanted to do...
...with me.
You trusted me before I ever trusted you.
So thank you.
Hey, stop that.
Don't you go making up how I feel.
It's so gross that I'm starting
to get goosebumps.
Something felt off.
Something just didn't feel right.
I finally got all of these followers,
and I pretty much had no obstacles.
I could finally have a world
where I'm at the center.
I basically became a god,
just like I planned...
...but somehow, it's no fun at all.
There's so much I just couldn't
understand with this guy.
Like why he didn't use his
psychic powers in his everyday life.
Or why he never went along
with my awesome ideas...
The fact that he could never
fully commit really annoyed me, too.
The only thing was... His desire to
make the girl he likes notice him...
I felt like that was something
I could somewhat relate to.
I want people to acknowledge me.
To know I exist.
After what happened with (LOL),
he noticed me, even though I was a ghost.
He didn't fear me. He didn't shun me.
In the end, he accepted me.
Back then, I thought I could use this guy...
But besides that, I felt something tensed up
in my heart slowly start to unravel.
Being with Shigeo, who has such little desire,
made me lose sight of my goal, too?
Wait, no. That's BS!
I'm going to lose my reason for being!
No, things are just getting started!
I... still have so much that
I want to do! I have ambitions!
Yeah, I know...
I'll hear you out.
About everything you want to do...
...as your friend.
Yeah... God and followers don't matter.
I never realized this until now,
but all I ever wanted...
...was a friend.
Shigeo... You're truly amazing.
Yeah, I'm done.
I'm going to stop messing
with everyone's minds.
I'm going to erase all memories
of the fake Psycho Helmet I created.
Then everyone will return to normal.
If the source of what's feeding
that worship energy disappears,
my godly powers will go away.
I'll return to normal as well.
Are you sure you're okay with this?
Wha--?!
Wasn't becoming a god your dream?
I'm giving that up because you kept coming
at me with "this is probably bad" logic!
I see. You're right.
Let's go home.
Yeah.
H-Hey, what's wrong, Shigeo?
It looks like I exerted too much power...
Well, of course this would happen, then!
Damn it... Why are you so awkward?
Fine.
Here.
You were basically like this every day when
you first joined the Body Improvement Club.
How long are you going to look like that?
It'll probably take about a week for me
to naturally lose my godly powers.
Actually, could you come back to my place
in about a week, then?
You sure don't hold back
sometimes, kid.
Oh, yeah. We need to do something
about this broccoli.
So how were you planning to get rid of it?
Lift it up with my telekinesis
and drop it into the ocean.
Huh? There's no way you could possibly...
Actually, the reason you terrify me is because
I can't finish that sentence with conviction.
This is such a fine broccoli.
It could've been an amazing tourist spot.
I feel a little bad,
but we don't have much choice.
People tend to get enamored by
anything mystical or overwhelming.
This broccoli will probably be in
the back of people's minds for a while.
I'm starting...
...to get really sleepy.
Can you wake me up when we get back home?
I ain't your servant, damn it!
Who the hell do you think I am?
Tch.
Don't you dare drool on me.
I did say, "Let's go home,"
but the truth is, I don't actually
have anywhere to go home to.
Now I've lost my goal, too.
I wonder what I should do.
Hey.
What?
Psycho Helmet...
But I'm not controlling
the Divine Tree anymore.
Wh-Who the hell are you?
Wait... I have a bad feeling about this.
The Divine Tree basically sucked up
my feelings along with all of the believers'
and has now gained consciousness.
If it's already gained a personality
called Psycho Helmet
and was patiently waiting to steal the authority
over this incredible amount of energy
that's lost control...
Leave that...
...behind.
He's sustenance.
Shigeo! Wake up right now!
We've got some real trouble on our hands!
Seriously?!
Wake up, Shigeo!
Now's really not the time to be sleeping!
It's no use... He won't wake up.
Godly Beam!
You bastards! Give Shigeo back, damn it!
Wait right here.
Hand him over... Hand him over...
Hand him over...
Hand him over.
Hup!
What the...?
Hand him over... Hand him over...
It's sucking up...
...all of my powers?!
Godly Beam!
Hand him over...
Hey, you're awake.
Can you move now?
Not yet... I can't move at all.
I can't really see, either.
Understood.
I think I heard something really loud.
Did something happen?
Nah, nothing. You probably dreamt it.
We're still not home yet?
Not yet. I took a little break.
I'm pretty exhausted myself.
I see...
Shigeo, this is the first time I've ever used
such an enormous amount of power.
You basically lived your life
holding in all this psychic power.
I think I finally understand
just how amazing that is.
Getting carried away because you were getting
noticed by girls is adorable in comparison.
It's only natural to get carried away
when you have this much power.
It's only natural to let this power
go to your head...
And yet, you...
You're a man. You're gonna be big.
My brainwashing would actually
work on Shigeo right now.
Listen carefully. These are
my first and final orders to you.
First, wake up. Stand up, Shigeo.
I don't have any strength left in my legs.
My arms won't move, either.
I know your body's wrecked, but stand up.
Even if you can't stand,
you need to do it.
And you need to walk
with your own two feet.
Go.
What about you, Dimple?
I have somewhere I need to stop by.
You go on ahead.
Okay.
Take care.
L-Let's go home.
Everyone, let's go home.
Even when I close my eyes, this ache lingers
The shade burns so much it's almost lost
Nii-san, there's some crazy news on TV right now,
but it's not you, right?
As we reluctantly part in our last moments
But it's not you, right?
Colored in navy blue, this hand reaches
for the missing piece
Colored in navy blue, this hand reaches for the missing piece
Just look at this! This was footage that was just filmed.
Colored in navy blue, this hand reaches
for the missing piece
Colored in navy blue, this hand reaches for the missing piece The
giant plant called the Divine Tree, which appeared out of nowhere,
The giant plant called the Divine Tree,
which appeared out of nowhere,
(Sign) Not lying to the point of bragging, the truth that isn't safe
The giant plant called the Divine Tree, which appeared out of nowhere,
(Sign) Not lying to the point of bragging,
the truth that isn't safe
(Sign) Not lying to the point of bragging, the truth that
isn't safe is floating and ascending into the atmosphere.
(Sign) Not lying to the point of bragging,
the truth that isn't safe
(Sign) Not lying to the point of bragging, the
truth that isn't safe What in the world is going on?
What in the world is going on?
(Chain) I suddenly realized that I was protected and
that you were close by What in the world is going on?
(Chain) I suddenly realized that I was protected
and that you were close by
(Chain) I suddenly realized that I was protected and that you were
close by |I don't know who's responsible, but why would they do this?
I don't know who's responsible,
but why would they do this?
(Pain) As I adorn this armor of ambition, this friendship is only partially
visible |I don't know who's responsible, but why would they do this?
(Pain) As I adorn this armor of ambition,
this friendship is only partially visible
(Pain) As I adorn this armor of ambition, this
friendship is only partially visible How strange...
(Pain) As I adorn this armor of ambition,
this friendship is only partially visible
(Pain) As I adorn this armor of ambition, this friendship is only partially
visible Oh, speaking of strange, my memories from this evening are a bit hazy.
Oh, speaking of strange, my memories
from this evening are a bit hazy.
(Remain) It's all right, I knew that from the start Oh, speaking
of strange, my memories from this evening are a bit hazy.
(Remain) It's all right,
I knew that from the start
(Remain) It's all right, I knew that from the
start Is that happening to you, too, Nii-san?
(Remain) It's all right,
I knew that from the start
(Exist...Exist...)
(Exist...Exist...) I can't remember,
either. I don't even know how I got home.
I can't remember, either.
I don't even know how I got home.
Whoa, yes... you're not alone I can't remember,
either. I don't even know how I got home.
Whoa, yes... you're not alone
You, too?
Whoa, yes... you're not alone It
might have been group hypnosis, then...
Whoa, yes... you're not alone
Anything suspicious like this
is Dimple's area of expertise.
Whoa, just... accept that Anything suspicious
like this is Dimple's area of expertise.
Whoa, just... accept that
I'll ask him the next time I see him.
Nii-san? Are you okay?
Whoa, just... accept that
Whoa, just... accept that Yeah.
But I just want to lie down for a bit.
Yeah. But I just want
to lie down for a bit.
English Translator: Michelle Tymon Translation Editor:
Zachary Carlysle Translation Checker: Sriram Gurunathan
English Translator: Michelle Tymon Translation Editor: Zachary
Carlysle Translation Checker: Sriram Gurunathan |I can't remember.
English Translator: Michelle Tymon Translation Editor:
Zachary Carlysle Translation Checker: Sriram Gurunathan
I can't remember, but...
Dimple, thank you...
You were my friend, Dimple.
Um, I'm sorry, what?
Going up to the summit of
Mt. Mud Boat to summon UFOs?
And I'm supposed to drive you?
You can't be serious!
Next time on Mob Psycho 100 Il Episode 7:
"Transmission 1
- Winter Break~."
Home video? Yes, indeed,
that is a wise decision.
"Transmission 1 - Winter Break~" Home
video? Yes, indeed, that is a wise decision.
"Transmission 1
- Winter Break~"